<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Design Pattern Samples</string>

    <!--Creational patterns -->
    <string name="title_builder">Builder</string>
    <string name="title_abstract_factory">Abstract Factory</string>
    <string name="title_factory">Factory</string>
    <string name="title_prototype">Prototype</string>
    <string name="title_singleton">Singleton</string>

    <!--Structural patterns -->
    <string name="title_adapter">Adapter</string>
    <string name="title_bridge">Bridge</string>
    <string name="title_composite">Composite</string>
    <string name="title_decorator">Decorator</string>
    <string name="title_facade">Facade</string>
    <string name="title_flyweight">Flyweight</string>
    <string name="title_proxy">Proxy</string>

    <!--Behavioral patterns -->
    <string name="title_chain_of_responsibility">Chain Of Responsibility</string>
    <string name="title_command">Command</string>
    <string name="title_iterator">Iterator</string>
    <string name="title_mediator">Mediator</string>
    <string name="title_memento">Memento</string>
    <string name="title_observer">Observer</string>
    <string name="title_state">State</string>
    <string name="title_strategy">Strategy</string>
    <string name="title_template">Template Method</string>
    <string name="title_visitor">Visitor</string>

    <!-- About Activity-->
    <string name="libraries">Libraries</string>
    <string name="info_design_patterns_app_icon">Design Patterns App Icon</string>
    <string name="template_app_version" translatable="false">v%1$s</string>
    <string name="menu_view_source_code">View Source Code</string>
    <string name="title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>


    <!--Main Activity-->
    <string name="info_design_pattern_image">Puzzle piece image as design pattern card icon</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_update_success">Yaay! App Updated</string>
    <string name="app_update_cancelled">App Update Cancelled</string>
    <string name="app_update_failed">App Update Failed</string>

    <!--Design Pattern Detail Activity-->
    <string name="title_code_sample">Code Sample</string>

    <!--Settings Activity-->
    <string name="title_theme_preference">App Theme</string>
    <string name="key_theme_preference" translatable="false">theme</string>
    <string name="pref_summary_theme_system_above_q">System Default</string>
    <string name="pref_summary_theme_system_below_q">Set By Battery Saver</string>
    <string name="pref_summary_theme_light">Light Theme</string>
    <string name="pref_summary_theme_dark">Dark Theme</string>

    <!--Design Pattern Descriptions-->
    <string name="desc_abstract_factory">
        A creational design pattern that encapsulates a group of individual factories that have a
        common theme without specifying their concrete classes.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_adapter">
        A structural design pattern that lets incompatible interfaces work in harmony by providing a
        wrapper to make the existing classes work without modifying the source code using one of the
        existing interfaces.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_bridge">
        A structural design pattern that decouples abstractions from their implementation.It has a
        very similar structure to the adapter pattern.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_builder">
        A creational design pattern that provides stepwise construction of complex objects.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_chain_of_responsibility">
        A behavioral design pattern consisting of a chain of receivers known as handlers,each handler
        will process a request and pass it on to the next for further processing.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_command">
        A behavioral design pattern  behavioral design pattern in which an object is used to
        encapsulate all information needed to perform an action or trigger an event at a later time.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_composite">
        A structural design pattern where a group of objects are treated as one.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_observer">
        A behavioral design pattern where an object known as a publisher maintains a list of objects
        known as observers which get notified on state changes.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_state">
        A behavioral design pattern where an object alters its behaviours when its internal state
        changes.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_decorator">
        A structural design patterns that adds behavior to an object using a wrapper without
        altering the structure of affected objects.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_facade">
        A structural design pattern that abstracts complexities by providing a simplified interface.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_factory">
        A creational design pattern which provides an interface to create
        objects at runtime.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_singleton">
        A creational design pattern that ensures the created object has only one instance.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_mediator">
        A behavioral design pattern that enforces loose coupling between objects by reducing
        communication complexity in how they interact.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_memento">
        A behavioral design that provides abiity to restore an object to its previous state.It is
        implemented with three objects: the originator, a caretaker and a memento.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_prototype">
        A creational design pattern which copies an existing instance of an object and making
        customization changes as opposed to creating a new object.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_proxy">
        A structural design pattern that provides a placeholder object that helps with access control
        to the original object by implementing an extra layer of encapsulation.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_strategy">
        A behavioral design pattern that selects an algorithm to use from a family of algorithms
        during runtime.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_template_method">
        The template method falls under behavioral design patterns.It constitutes of a method in a
        superclass, usually an abstract superclass, and defines the skeleton of an operation in
        terms of a number of high-level steps. These steps are themselves implemented by additional
        helper methods in the same class as the template method.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_visitor">
        A behavioral design pattern that lets you add new operations to existing objects without
        modifying their structure by separating the algorithm from the objects structure.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_iterator">
       A behavioral design pattern in which an iterator is used to traverse a container and
        access the container\'s elements.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_flyweight">
        A structural design pattern that reduces the number of objects created by fitting more objects
        into the available amount of RAM by sharing common parts of state between multiple objects
        hence decreasing memory footprint and increasing performance.

        It may seem similar to singleton however there should be only one Singleton instance,once
        the required object is created, we cannot create more. whereas a Flyweight class can have
        multiple instances with different extrinsic attributes provided by the client.In this case
        the time of day.
    </string>


</resources>
